There are some CSCs too, whose
CSC ID will be deleted or suspended,
after that you will neither be
able to login to your CSC ID nor will
you be able to avail any service from your CSC portal,
so what should you do in such a situation so that
your CSC ID is not deleted, friends, from
when will the CSC ID start getting deleted,
this is what we are going to tell you in today's video, so
friends, first of all
we will talk about this news, this is the news that the HD
of our CSC has
tweeted, so first of all we will
show you his tweet,
what has he tweeted and what is the reason for
deleting or suspending the CSC ID,
so here friends, the HD of CSC A Governance,
our Mr. Sanjay K Rakesh
ji has tweeted here,
if you people have been following his Twitter account, then
you must have also got this news,
if you have got the news
or not, then only we
give you information here and here you people
can see that he has
tweeted here that it is important that many people are following the
CSC  And are applying for UCL, I
want to tell all of you that many people are
not doing any work even after getting the ID,
we are keeping a close eye on such people, soon the
inactive IDs will be banned, this is the
last chance for such people, so here
they have clearly said that many
people who have taken ICC ID
and many people have
taken Aadhar UCL along with CSC ID
but they are not doing any work, are
not doing any transaction with their CSC ID, the
CSC account of such people will be
suspended, after that you will
neither be able to do any work with your CC ID
nor will you be able to login to your CSC ID,
so friends,
if you are not doing any work on your CSC ID, then soon
your CSC ID i.e. CC account will also be
suspended, so you also
want that your CSC account,
CSC ID, should not be deleted, so in such a situation,
you have to do some
transaction in it right now and at this very moment, friends, if you have a
CSC bank account.  If you are running DCB then
you have to do minimum 25 transactions in a month, so
in such a situation, to save your CSC ID from getting
suspended, you will have to do
transactions in it, so friends, as we
just showed you the tweet which
our Anti Sir had tweeted,
he has clearly written in it that
if you people do not do any transaction on your CSC portal, then in
such a situation your
CSC account will be suspended
permanently, so I hope
friends, you must have liked today's video, if you
liked the video then
like the video and also subscribe to the channel.